I call to order the regular scheduled meeting of Miami City Council, Monday March 6th, 2023.
Public input on schedule personal appearances? We have none three consent agenda staff recommends we
approve items four and five six budget amendment proceeding and expending insurance recovery from
cvb office damage settlement preceding an expanding CESF number 20-E 12 by 128 sorry
I thought it would be grant monies for computer equipment receiving and expending
the Oklahoma humanities let's talk about a grant proceeding and expanding from Vance Chevrolet first
responder program of vehicle repair and receding spending juvenile alcohol fund
money to reimburse for school resource officer training so budget amendment 23-15
is doing all those things we're receding in
the funds that we've received for insurance recovery grants donations and other
and then we're moving into the expense all of these are
The insurance recovery and or grants. All
Of the funds were being spent as what their intent was to
seven other new business if any which is risen since posting this agenda
eight staff reports nine mayor council community announcements
And I got one here um
The Stotts family of course many of you know we lost chuck stops a few days ago his funerals today
Chuck was
A huge part
Of our community he's around here a long time probably
A record for how
Many years one guy
Was the manager
Of a walmart in the same location I don't know that's
A record but i'd say it probably pretty close
But if you could keep their family and your prayers
Um I know they would appreciate it um pretty good size funeral today
So those were there
And uh the family's gonna have a hard time for a while
The walmart employees are going to have
A hard time
For a while
i don't know if you've been in wal-mart since but
I went in a couple days ago and just felt weird
It's used to walking any seat you saw chuck there somewhere
Um kind of like high tower
You guys were about the same height with me
So
There was big presence
They're that it's not
Their now so
Weird vibe when
You walk into wal-mart now at least for me
So you can keep all those folks in your prayers
Ken city manager communications
I was really proud that our pd
They were very grateful for the work
That you all did being not only present there with
Our motorcycles to lead
All the way into kansas working
With
All the communities
I don't know stepping on both times here
But whenever they left the church
i forgot about that part of a great moment
When we got to the light
Of the church everybody stopped
Took up the hearse
They went across
The street and did one last lap around wal-mart
And he came back out
Headed on to kansas
But it was kind of a cool little tribute
Chuck's last